<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alireza Shiasi</title>
    <link>https://alirezashiasi.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Alireza Shiasi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:13:05 +0330</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alirezashiasi.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Connect!</title>
      <link>https://alirezashiasi.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:49:19 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alirezashiasi.com/contact/</guid>
      
        <description>I’m always happy to connect with like-minded professionals, explore opportunities, or simply chat about ideas and innovations.
Social Media You can reach me via social media, find me here and there:
Linkedin - For professional connections and collaborations Instagram - My personal space. Note: It’s private, but feel free to send me a request Github - Explore my projects and contributions If you prefer other ways to reach me, drop me a message on LinkedIn, and I’ll get back to you as soon as I can!</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Info &amp; Interests</title>
      <link>https://alirezashiasi.com/personal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:43:25 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alirezashiasi.com/personal/</guid>
      
        <description>Personal Writing and poetry have always been my way of expressing ideas and emotions, offering a creative outlet that connects me with the world in unique ways. I&amp;rsquo;m deeply passionate about sustainability and driving sustainable business development, focusing on innovative solutions that create lasting impact. Open-source advocacy and Linux hold a special place in my journey, reflecting my belief in collaboration and transparency to inspire growth and innovation.
Art, especially music, enriches my life, as do exploring new perspectives and fostering creativity in everything I do.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awards &amp; Achievements</title>
      <link>https://alirezashiasi.com/awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:50:10 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alirezashiasi.com/awards/</guid>
      
        <description> Martyrs Memorial Design Award: Recognized for the construction consulting and innovative design of the martyrs memorial at the University of Abbaspour. Event Management Success: Successfully launched and managed Mohtavagaran, a series of events focused on content creation and marketing, attracting industry experts and professionals. Idea Bazaar Recognition: Selected as one of the top participants in the Idea Bazaar event at the University of Tehran. </description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education &amp; Credentials</title>
      <link>https://alirezashiasi.com/edu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:23:15 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alirezashiasi.com/edu/</guid>
      
        <description>Academics University of Tehran, MSc. in Corporate Entrepreneurship | Tehran, Iran Feb. 2022 - Dec. 2024
Thesis: “Identifying organizational mechanisms affecting sustainable business model innovation” Supervisors: Dr. Mehran Rezvani, Dr. Mohammad Reza Zali Payame Noor University, MSc. in Software Engineering (Incomplete) Pursued studies out of strong interest in technology and systems design. Islamic Azad University, Bachelor of Civil Engineering| Tehran, Iran 2009 - 2014
PUBLICATION Thesis: “Identifying organizational mechanisms affecting sustainable business model innovation”, by Alireza Shiasi, University of Tehran, Faculty of Entrepreneurship.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Experience</title>
      <link>https://alirezashiasi.com/exp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:22:53 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alirezashiasi.com/exp/</guid>
      
        <description>Founder, Business Developer &amp;amp; CM Najarch | Tehran, Iran | Dec 2020 - PRESENT
Architectural &amp;amp; Engineering Sustainable Initiatives
Designed and implemented a sustainable business model for architectural and engineering services. Provided business development and marketing consultancy, leading to client recognition and partnerships, including Shahid Beheshti University. Honored by Shahid Beheshti University for excellence in design services and consultancy. Two factories design &amp;amp; construction consulting done in less than two years.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://alirezashiasi.com/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:12:21 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alirezashiasi.com/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      
        <description>First Post Introduction This is bold text, and this is emphasized text.
Visit the Hugo website!</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>